Gorilla
Tsubasa-sama
Sensei's writing lyrics
Yes, it just started happening
Do you think it could be a new song?
Gorilla
Strange one
Strange face
Bungee
Bungee?
Chihiri's amazing!
Ever since the trial broadcast
her popularity has skyrocketed
She's been getting more solo work too
That's what they call explosive popularity
Yeah, she's had so much on her plate
that she hasn't had a chance
to go to the amphitheater lately
Oh man, I'm worried for her
If she's this popular
it might affect the outcome
of the general election
Oh man, I'm worried for her
If she's this popular
It might affect the outcome
of the general elections
That was quite a speech
Well done, Chihiri
I wouldn't be surprised at all
if she's elected after that
Oh right, the general elections
Oh, so I've forgotten all about that
Oh, so not fair
The voting has already started
The CD that comes with the ballot
is seeing an explosive increase
in the number of downloads
The CD that comes with the ballot
is seeing an explosive increase
in the number of downloads
Crap!
So they're really going through with it?
In a future where humankind
has gone into space
and a ban has been placed on entertainment
Idol group AKB-0048
continues to perform illegal concerts
These girls put their lives on the line
and sing brilliantly
acquiescates
By missing out
Chihiri
You step back
I want to shake
what
шеおれそうな長い坂の前
未来があるなら 背を向けられない
友よ、覚えている会?
あの日誓い合ったこの場所
季節の花が咲く
主なきその声
聞こえるよ
太陽がほら少しずつあたりのその闇を剥がしてくれるだろう
主なきさあこの時に僕たちはそう歩き出そう
誰もみんな弱い生き物さ愛の気配探しながら滝へ進む
スープ・一定をルーチに出し
威ionarON グラリラチャンネルル?
We will create a Guerrilla channel for Zero Zero and broadcast it on television
And you want us to appear on the show?
That's right.
We are honored to consider youook that you could take the first broadcast for us, but what exactly would we do?
IT'S A TV show, What question is that?!
You can't blame her. On Lancaster, the only TV we got was news and weather.
What? You're kidding me!
Lancaster's had a long-standing entertainment band. It makes sense.
Makota-san's home planet is Naniwa Star, which is famous for its comedy shows.
So to people from Lancaster, she's a comedy alien? Stop that!
But Nagisa, haven't you seen any TV since we left home?
With all the lessons and studying, I haven't had time to check it out.
As far as AKB is concerned, TV shows often request members for guest appearances.
That's true for the successors, but from now on, the trainees will appear alongside the regulars on our variety show.
What do we do on a variety show? Is it fun?
No way! Please don't die! Please don't die! Please don't die! Please don't die! Please don't die!
Nice knowing ya!
Wait, you're telling me...
This is a variety show!
Oh!
Here I go!
I can't! I want to go home!
I can't! I can't! Just get me down right now!
Take me home! I can't do this!
I can't! I can't! I can't do this!
I look so stupid!
Your reaction was brilliantly performed! Good job!
It wasn't a performance!
Bungee jumping's a difficult place to start our careers in television!
Hey, Suzuko, are variety shows nothing but death-defying stunts?
Oh, no. It's called Variety for a reason.
They'll compete to make the fun of this.
Uh, this is so embarrassing.
Can I forfeit?
I see. Do they do anything else?
Some shows have their participants cook food.
Um, Mamori-san, don't you think that outfit
is a bit too revealing?
Done. Looks tasty, right?
Oh, this isn't that kind of show.
Huh?
There are also talk shows.
Uh, do you want to know what my most sacred treasure is?
Well, probably this brunchie.
Mom made it for me just before I joined the group.
Um, my mom's a homemaker, by the way.
She's really great.
And my parents married for love. It wasn't her own.
Oh, I can't talk in front of people
without rehearsing at first. It's impossible.
Why couldn't I make anyone laugh?
I thought the faces you made were very funny.
Keep your chin up.
Those weren't faces! I was freaking out!
And here I thought it'd be like performing
or doing handshake events.
I'm glad I got to do it with the rest of you.
Can you imagine doing this by yourself,
like Jerry is right now?
Oh, yeah.
I forgot.
By herself?
Just thinking about it makes my stomach hurt!
Mmm.
Oh.
Chonchi!
Are you feeling tired?
Huh?
No, I'm fine.
Why do you ask?
Really?
You seem down in the dumps to me.
You've been really popular lately.
There are rumors that you must have found
some good sponsors.
Just who might they be?
Thank you very much.
Oh, Jerry!
Oh, good morning, Yuko.
Do you have a gravure shoot as well today?
Yep.
It's time to make sweet love to the camera.
Chonchi!
Hurry up!
Kay!
Catch you later, Ival!
Okay.
Critical failure.
Another one?
We can't afford these setbacks.
Chierry, you must shine more, my daughter.
Shine for Zodiac.
Nice frown.
Where'd you get it?
Something's bothering me.
Kasumagastar is an important government location.
I find it hard to believe that we escaped as easily as we did.
Ah.
So there must be an explanation.
It's just a feeling.
The Woda's intelligence force is looking into it for me.
Oh, 5 a.m. call times are getting old fast.
Oh, being on TV is exhausting to boot.
Really?
I've been having an absolute ball.
It's a great chance to get out there so that the fans remember us.
The lady's got a point there.
Well, at least some of us are keeping the enthusiasm alive.
Well, we still have our stage performances and lessons as usual, so we better eat a lot
to keep up our stamina.
But they're cutting back on performances.
Suppression of entertainment has gotten stricter, and the DES attacks have become more intense.
We can't help it.
But if we have time to be appearing on TV, shouldn't we be performing concerts instead?
Hey, what's with all the frowning?
Always wear a smile and give it everything you've got!
Takamina-san!
I know you're not used to being on TV since you only just started,
but I'm sure you have something to gain from doing it.
Okay.
Oh, Nagisa, got a minute?
I understand you haven't made posters for the general elections yet.
Is that right?
Oh, if there's anything you don't know, just ask.
I'd be happy to help you out with it.
See ya!
Right.
I'll be sure to come see you.
The general elections, huh?
I had forgotten about them.
Let the first AKB-0048 Impressions Contest begin!
This is my impression of third-generation Ayaka singing.
That was my impression of the Buddhist snoring at night.
And so, this has been my impression of Yuko-san,
who fell asleep clinging to Sayaka-san.
Fury!
Fury time!
Yeah!
Amazing!
Thank you very much.
For my impression, I'll be imitating this Kira-
Stop!
Stop the cameras!
This taping is over!
I've been watching quietly since we started working on the show, but...
This is terrible!
But we were thrust into this without any experience!
Do I have to teach you how to do everything?
I don't deny the benefits of working on TV.
And I realize that we don't necessarily have a knack for every aspect of this.
But what we are good at is putting on concerts.
I agree with her, especially now that the ban on entertainment has been tightened.
Shouldn't we be performing even more concerts?
Big sis...
You should think hard about the meaning of that, and what it is you're doing.
There's a goddou...
Yay!
Noo quixir
Nagisa?
I haven't seen you dance in a while.
It was amazing. You know, out of all of us, I think you shine the most when you're singing and dancing.
Oh, my bad. I didn't mean to imply that you're not good at anything else. Sorry about that.
So, Chiri, what's bothering you?
I can't focus on my work.
I wonder if it's only because people are talking about the trial and I'm not actually popular.
That's not true at all. It's because they were all so moved by your words.
I'm not so sure.
Chiri.
What I want is for people to appreciate me for my abilities. I don't want to be elected for any other reason.
Oh! It's Nagi-san and Chiri!
Chiri?
You're still practicing at this hour?
Yukaren-san, Koji-haru-san.
Oh? You're not sure if your popularity is real or not? Don't be silly.
So that's why you argued with Tsubasa-san about wanting to put on concerts.
You two haven't made your posters for the general elections yet, right?
Oh, no.
I've been putting it off.
Then it might be a good idea for you two to take a look at it.
I definitely agree!
Viewing party time!
I have no idea what you're talking about.
The previous general elections, silly!
It's footage of the 13th generation, Medea Atsuko-san.
What is that? It's so bright!
Everyone, thank you so much!
Ah-chan!
Thank you!
That voice!
Oh, it was her!
We want to give it to them!
That voice!
It belonged to the 13th A-chan!
And this is...
the shine of the center nova.
I only wish we could become lights and keep shining down on everyone
with our love forever and ever.
It's inspiring!
I really hope I can be like A-chan someday.
Me too!
She's the best!
From this day forward, the 13th A-chan is my rival!
In the next year's general elections, I will...
I will definitely beat A-chan and become the next center nova!
Just you watch!
Is that Yuko-san?
Yeah, and if I'm right, this was filmed before she took over the name Yuko.
Wow.
When she was a trainee like us, she was already challenging her seniors.
Yuko is incredible!
I can feel just how serious Yuko-san is!
Now let's go out there and say, pretty cool smile!
Ready?
Let's give it everything we have!
I'm with you, big sis!
Okay!
What happened to Kanata-san?
Yesterday, Suzuko-san did some research afterward.
Our program's only going to be broadcast on planets with bands.
Especially the super strict ones we may not be able to get to.
These planets are apparently so locked down that even public gatherings are shut down with extreme force!
No way!
We can't go to perform concerts, but we can still reach out to them, using their underground networks.
Our TV show could reach a whole new audience!
Huh?
Whoa!
If we lose this, we have to face the penalty game!
We're screwed!
The minute we were put against Kanata, our chances of winning this thing became slim to none!
It's way too soon to be giving up!
Huh?
If we're going to do this, let's give it everything we have!
Whoa!
Nice catch!
Guess she's out!
Whoa!
Memori-san!
You're close!
Oopsie!
Ha ha ha ha!
Ah!
Memori!
What do you say we give that another go?
Oh!
Ah!
You're right!
It's beautiful!
Amazing!
We're already been performing a concert!
And Memori-san's Kirara is shining like there's no tomorrow!
The audience is having fun too!
And so am I!
Let's go!
Well let's go!
And the one of the best 2014 4K pratic com volunteered
And the advance of infrastructure
the world of the planet!
I'm following a sec though!
We're Bonifino-san!
And here's the fastest time!
Let's go!
Oh!
All four!
Mm!
Oiree, nice one!
That's it! Because we're serious!
Because we're really having fun!
Yeah!
We're here!
I think it's safe to say that even Kanata can lose at some things.
Whether it's a concert or anything else,
conveying our true feelings is important!
We just wanna make things we know!
Why, why?
They're looking good today!
What were you doing?
That sins we can come in
Yeah!
That's beautiful!
It's cuộc veces!
I still don't really understand the general election, but...
Thanks, everyone!
Bye!
Thank you! Bye!
What's going on? The power's out!
I can't see anything! Everyone stay calm!
I am the manager for AKB-0048, Tsubasa Katigiri.
What is she doing?
Tonight, I'll be delivering some special news,
some that I'm sure you'll be excited about,
regarding the new single general elections.
She's doing this now? Why here?
What do you think she's announcing?
Well, if I had to guess, she probably has the current rankings.
Here it comes!
We have ten members who will be selected for this election.
They've all worked hard, so show them your appreciation.
Number ten, ninth generation, Rei Kitihara.
Number nine, seventy-seventh generation trainee, Chiari Sono.
Number one, three, six, foxes.
The finalnaire...
pee??
Ah...
J...
いつかの願いは 土の中で眠って 約束の時刻に 希望の目立てるんだ
二人が出会った頃 夢など まだ種だった
それくらい時が過ぎ 花は咲くのだろう
この涙を君に捧ぐ もっと君が輝くなら
ずっと見守ってた 深奥の空から
今僕は雨になろう
Ah...
君に捧ぐ こんな僕にできることは
君の虚しさを 少しでも癒すことさ
僕は雨になろう
君の虚しさを 少しでも癒すことができる
ジュアルの大演出で うちにلكも一緒
The general elections.